<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Protocols on Harmony</title>
    <link>https://harmonyapp.io/protocol/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Protocols on Harmony</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="https://harmonyapp.io/protocol/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://harmonyapp.io/protocol/rest/rest/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://harmonyapp.io/protocol/rest/rest/</guid>
      <description>RESTful Endpoints Authentication If an endpoint expects authentication, the user should set the Authorization header to a valid token from the gRPC API.
POST /_harmony/media/upload Expects authentication: yes
The body should be POST-ed as a multipart form (multipart/form-data), with a single part named file which contains the body of the file being uploaded.
URL Parameters  filename: The name of the file being uploaded. contentType: The MIME type of the file.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Formatting</title>
      <link>https://harmonyapp.io/protocol/chat/v1/formatting/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://harmonyapp.io/protocol/chat/v1/formatting/</guid>
      <description>Clients are expected to support the Commonmark specification for all message text, with the following changes:
 Images (![]()) should be explicitly ignored by the client &amp;lt;@123456789&amp;gt; should be interpreted as a user mention, and render as the specified user&amp;rsquo;s display name, with other decoration optional &amp;lt;@|123456789&amp;gt; should be interpreted as a role mention, and render as the specified role&amp;rsquo;s name and colour, with other decorations optional &amp;lt;:123456789:&amp;gt; should be interpreted as a local emoji, and render as the emoji&amp;rsquo;s content as provided by the homeserver of the guild &amp;lt;:123456789|homeserver.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Server Name Resolution</title>
      <link>https://harmonyapp.io/protocol/name-resolution/name-resolution/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://harmonyapp.io/protocol/name-resolution/name-resolution/</guid>
      <description>Every Harmony homeserver is identified by a &amp;ldquo;server name.&amp;rdquo; A server name uniquely identifies a server, regardless of whether the resolved IP address changes or not. Two server names pointing to the same IP address would be considered two different homeservers.
A server name is resolved to an IP address and port using the following process:
When IP Address (xxx.xxx.xxx.xxx + optional :port) When the server name is an IP address, this is the resolved IP of the server that requests should be sent to.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>